What will you do when you have brought so many laddus on every branch?   I will
distribute one laddu each, I will not feed you to your fill.
Shivam come here.
Yes ma'am.   Have you
brought the bike?   I have
brought a scooter, not a bike.
Is there a diggi in it?
Yes, there is a diggi.
Take this and put it in that.  I will take it from you on the way.
Okay ma'am.   Do
n't tell anyone otherwise I will beat you badly.
Okay ma'am, don't tell me.
Yes, go.
[laughter]
Ma'am is making him laugh, look, shut up, the
land of my country spews gold, diamonds and
pearls, the land of my country [laughter]
look how much I am telling you, look, I will
slap you on your face, the
land of my country spews gold, diamonds and pearls, the
land of my country,
Jai Hind, Jai Bharat.  [Applause]
[Cheering] The
next contestant is Shivam, who will give a speech in English.
Good morning all of you.  My name is Shivam
Mishra.
Good.
Today India is our country.
Our Country.
[laughter] He has
come out, that's why don't you remember, go and sit
[applause]
Next contestant, why should the kick fall, the
leaf does not move, the wind moves it, the leaf does
not move, the wind moves it, Hindustan does
not bring Pakistan to war [laughter] The
next contestants are Pinky Priya Komal who will
perform their dance on the patriotic song Yahan
Hai Dharti
[music] of
this place, so
today's program ends here.
All the children will come to school from tomorrow.
Sir, are there not enough laddus?   Did you
fall short?  How did it fall short?  I went and asked the children to bring
laddus.   Don't know.   No
problem, order more.  OK sir.
What happened madam, why are you staying here?   Oh,
nothing happened.  I am waiting for Shivam.
You guys come, I am coming with him.
Okay, I'll leave.
Yes, let's go.
All the children left.  Not yet arrived.
[music]
Oh
[laughter]